It's Monday.
How you doing, huh?
Love the potatoes.
Saturn.
City.
Love your playthroughs, Oliver.
No spoiler, actually blind playthroughs are extremely good to watch.
Hey man, I'm glad you're enjoying it.
I'm having fun.
As long as I'm having fun, I'm gonna keep doing it.
But thanks for saying that.
I appreciate it, man.
Keep watching.
Saturn.
Best day of the week.
Is it North Star?
Is it really?
You probably also enjoy waking up at 6am, huh?
Literally joined the stream the moment you said hi.
Perfect timing, then.
What's up, Enzo?
How are you doing?
Isanti made a microwave potato today?
I'm so proud of you.
Well done.
Greetings from Poland.
Hey there, Pawel.
Is your name actually Pawel Gawel?
Because that's an awesome name.
If that's true.
I mean, I bet your real name is Pawel, but Gawel also?
It even rhymes.
Sarasat damn finally caught it live.
Now I can't go to the gym, otherwise I'd miss it.
Hey, go to the gym.
Watch the VOD.
Get out of here.
Don't watch me.
Go to the gym.
Sarasat, I'm just kidding.
Do whatever you want.
Go to the gym and have me in your ear.
GW flips.
Hey Oliver.
And the fans missed the Subnautica days.
Oh, that's a long time ago.
First time I can truly watch live.
I'm watching this while at the hospital with my mom.
Oh man, I hope for nothing terrible.
In any case, thanks for being here and checking it out.
Welcome, welcome.
News of PE.
By the way, Oliver, will Noida be videos or stream?
I hope it streams.
Yeah, I think it's going to be a stream.
It seems like a good stream game.
I don't know why, but it sort of strikes me as a game similar to Rainworld.
And Rainworld was a fantastic stream game.
So, yeah.
Out of wild times, huh?
Man, that feels like an eternity ago.
It's over a year.
Can you believe it?
Anyway, guys, I'm gonna close you down.
No offense.
You're gone.
Just like that.
Magic.
And now, I gotta remind myself what I was doing in here last time.
Expert.
Let's go.
Because I'm an expert gamer.
Of course, I require the expert difficulty.
I'm not an expert gamer.
I am a very practiced gamer.
A very seasoned gamer.
I've been gaming my whole life.
So, if there's a challenge, I'll surely overcome it in time.
What was I even doing last time?
I have to get used to the controls again, it seems.
Remember what I was doing?
Right.
I had the idea of having a special chest where I just put everything in.
That I don't want to sort immediately and then sort it later.
I think I may do that with the top ones here.
I think I already started doing that, didn't I?
So, let's do something like this.
Deposit all.
Everything goes in.
And then I want to determine what I want to keep for now.
Oh, yeah!
Right!
I did kill the bee, didn't I?
And I got this.
Hold on, did I ever check what I could use this for?
It's a material.
Wait a minute.
Bradley?
Real quick, tell me about this hurtful beekeeper.
Oh, it's one of the ingredients for this crazy sword.
Can I actually make that?
Hold on.
I have this, I have that, I don't have this.
Oh, I don't have any of these.
A hundred?!
Where do I cause the stars to rain from?
Where do I even find this?
Meowmir?
Is that a reference to Daromir?
Terrorblade?
My goodness.
Oh, yeah, I have two.
So I forgot to check this last time.
I remember at some point I checked both of these.
And the nimble molten pickaxe was actually a little worse in certain scenarios.
Whereas the Deathbringer pickaxe was better in some.
It's a little bit weird, I gotta do some more testing, so I'll leave those here for now.
The strange brew.
I don't think I need that right now.
Let's put that in potions.
In you go.
The unpleasant imp staff.
I kind of forgot about that last time when I was doing the bee fight.
I should have summoned these.
Totally forgot about that.
Speaking of summons, I do want to try to make something very special.
Hold on.
Where is this?
Wait, where did I just deposit everything I had?
Oh, I put it here.
I wanted to check the bee stuff.
The honey.
The grenades.
Oh, yeah, I had the bee grenades, so whatever.
The hive wand.
That's such a weird item.
It's not a material.
Bee nade and bee wax.
Hive.
I kind of forgot if there was anything useful with that.
I need to check it again.
Right.
Live crystals.
God damn it.
I can throw that in the shimmer and it will actually be an amazing thing.
Not only that, but I need to make what you might call it.
I need to make more of the mana crystals.
If that's the name.
Michelinius, where did I put my thingies?
So usually I have them here, my stars, but I think I put them somewhere else.
Are they hiding in one of these inventories, maybe?
Oh, this one's empty.
That's nice.
This one.
Man, look how clean that is.
I'm proud of myself.
That's nice.
That's very clean.
Quick stack.
All right, that's been stacked.
Let's see here.
Live crystal.
Where's my... Oh, wait, do I even need... Yeah, I need the stars.
Where did I put them?
Did I put them?
Fallen stars.
But didn't I have more than 12?
I seem to remember having over 100.
Maybe I used them to craft something, but I will check everything.
Let's see here.
I have no more gems on me.
What's this?
Oh, it's bait.
That's bait.
That is bait.
Let's see here.
We have...
Let's go up and sell it.
Why am I storing this?
This one is also... I'm going to sell that.
It's not a material, so whatever.
The honey block was kind of important.
More hive.
Happy birthday, hive.
Let's take the bones.
Oh, wait, the bones can stay here, actually.
Hook.
Let's see.
You know what?
All these weird torches here, I can just remove them.
I don't really want these specialized torches anyway.
The geysers can be removed.
Let's do some spring cleaning here, huh?
Now this, the solar tablet fragment, was also kind of important.
I think that's the key to getting inside of that temple that I found on the ground.
But I'm just not sure how that's going to work out in practice.
Okay, really quickly.
Ludo, you are now my go-to shop man.
Will you buy things from me?
Take this water gun and also take the geysers.
Actually, these sell for something.
That's nice.
And the rope.
You can have 3,400 pieces of rope.
You can do whatever you want with it.
One grenade.
I don't want to sell that.
Okay, this looks good so far.
Now, I'm pretty sure I had more stars than 12, so let me just check everything.
Oh, here's an idea.
If I click this button now and look where the stars go, maybe that's an indicator.
Aha!
I'm a fucking genius!
Ho, ho, ho!
God damn!
I'm good!
Wow, that was smart.
That was smart.
Let's see here.
Wait, what's this?
Yo, hold on now.
Oh, I need to make these.
I wonder how many I can make of these, so hold on.
How many did I start with?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
So that's 20 hearts in total.
So I started with five hearts, right?
So maybe I need 15 of these, assuming I can only upgrade as many times as here.
But then again, there's only 200 mana.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll just make... I mean, it doesn't really matter.
I need a nun for that.
I have a nun.
Let's make 15.
There we go.
And then I have life crystals that I all want to turn into that specialized life crystal.
Nice.
So that's one of the plans for today.
Take these to the magical liquid of dreams and upgrade my character.
The other thing I want to do is... let me actually grab these stars.
The other thing I want to do today is to first ask Bradley once more about the... was it the bee wax?
Yeah.
So I want to make... I want to make bee stuff.
And I want to make bee nades.
Even though I already have a bunch.
They seem pretty cool, honestly, but probably start with this.
We can do the bee nades later.
I want to make a hornet staff and I want to make all the gear.
And for that I need bee wax.
And you know what?
I don't have enough.
So we're going to be using the abomination to get more.
And this time...
Yoink!
And then I'm going to go up here.
Click on that and go yoink!
Now I have two of these.
It's going to make the fight easier.
Then we're going to head back to the beehive and kick some goddamn bee ass!
I thought I was about to say something else, weren't you?
Now the hive wand is a little bit mysterious to me.
So mysterious things I do not understand.
I can't go in the box of miscellaneous things.
Perfect.
I wonder if I can do Crimson Rod as well.
Oh wait, not that one, is it?
You know what?
This is not bad, is it?
Ah, 15 mana, actually.
It's kind of terrible.
It's shit.
You know what?
I'll sell it.
I will sell that shit.
Yeah, sort this stuff.
I have three shackles, that's definitely more than you need.
So let's sell two of them.
I also have the Crimson outfit there.
Okay, this looks good.
Ornate Shadow Key.
Oh yeah, right, that was the pet.
This is also a pet.
Maybe I should have a chest just for pets and stuff like that.
I have two Obsidian roses.
Maybe I only need one.
Let me sell it, but first let me quickly ask Bradley if there's anything I should be wary of here.
I can use this to make different things.
I have this already, don't I?
Yeah, I used that to make the Obsidian Shield, I believe.
Now, oh right!
This seems pretty sick.
Obsidian Water Walking Boots.
If I'm going to fight the Wall of Flesh, walking on lava seems insanely useful.
Because I always fall down, right?
And then I fall into the lava and I have to get up again and it costs me a bunch of time.
There could be a solution there.
Oh, and I want to fish for more crates, of course.
That's also something I want to do.
Miscellaneous Box, can you please open?
Nice.
The Honey Blocks, go in here, that's fine.
The Desert Torch can be sold.
What else?
Let's sell the Pink Gel.
Nobody wants that.
And these.
Let's just take enough space.
The Lawn Mower.
Do I really need this?
Wait, Most Pure and Hallowed Grass.
Mowed Grass reduces enemy spawn chance.
You know what's funny here?
That's kind of a crucial piece of information in this game, isn't it?
Mowed Grass reduces enemy spawn chance.
And how do I learn about it?
From a fucking item called the Lawn Mower.
If I hadn't seen this item, I wouldn't know of this.
So I'm curious how many other things are happening in this game.
That I don't know about because I haven't found the item for it.
Wouldn't that be amazing?
If there's so many more things to discover.
Now the Dynamite, I kind of want to sell that as well.
Okay, Ludo.
Will you take my Dynamite?
Also take my Shackle.
And the Rose.
Because I already have one.
You can have it.
It's yours.
This one, I kind of wish I had a better version of this.
Because it's so good, but it's not as good as the other ones I have.
This increases the strength of friendly bees.
Increases melee speed.
I keep saying that word wrong.
I have to get used to saying it the right way.
Ludo, can you also buy this stupid-ass Crimson Rod from me?
Thank you very much.
Can't fire as you can have.
Okay, alright.
Organics, let's put the Stinger in here.
Oh, I also wanted to sell that.
Take these.
The Sabinator is kind of big.
And I want it.
Let's keep it there.
The hurtful beekeeper.
I will save the sword until I have the full outfit and shit.
I want to judge it when I have all the good stuff first.
This one grenade.
Let's get rid of that one grenade.
It's taken off inventory and I don't like it.
In fact, I'm not a fan at all.
I can have this too.
Okay, let's do that and that.
The stone block.
Let's keep that for now.
Now again, Bradley.
I need to know about these fragments.
Summons the Eclipse.
I only need eight of these.
Yo, that sounds kind of badass.
I think I do remember where I got him even.
I got him from...
There was a guy I killed right here.
And I got the fragments there.
Maybe if I go back, he has respawned and I can get one more kill.
Leave it like that, I guess.
So I think I'm going to quickly do that as well today.
Check on that.
Man, I'm so happy.
I connected the world, by the way.
I can go here now to the cavern pylon.
Even though this is temporary, I want to make another cavern place.
I'm not too happy about this.
But let's actually do that now.
Oh, right click and then here.
And now we're going to be throwing things into the magical liquid.
Magical liquid of dreams.
MLOD.
Very important acronym you need to remember.
Let's see here.
Oh, I just made dirt.
That's fantastic.
Mana crystal.
Yoink!
It becomes an arcane crystal and then life crystal.
Let's take...
10 for now.
Nice.
Let's get them both.
Okay, let's see here.
Let's see now.
Permanently boosts life regeneration.
I wonder if there's a way to see my actual stats.
Like, is there a number to this life regeneration anywhere in the game, right?
That's what I'm wondering here.
Probably not.
Doink.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no, it was a one time thing.
Oh, no.
Oh, that's horrible.
Why did I make so many?
I should have tested with one.
I'm such an idiot.
I just assumed because I could use...
fuck.
Oh, hey, you know what?
That's something at least.
It's worth a shit ton of money.
Oh, but then again, it's worth even more without having been modified.
Well, shit.
They're not materials, so I guess I sell them.
Okay.
You can have the dirt.
Well, at least we tested it, right?
Let me try the fallen star.
I don't remember if I ever tried that.
Just a straight up star.
Throw it in there.
Let's go to the MLOD.
One of them pop.
Oh,
oh, disappears after the sunrise.
I wonder if that's what just happened.
It's day right now, isn't it?
It must be day right now.
Oh, almost fell in.
Actually, that's a good way to get down again.
This is actually kind of useful.
That's a nice way to get back down.
Do you sell anything else?
Anything of note?
Okay, let's go back to...
Actually, let's do the B now.
Actually, I got to go back first.
Oh, it's so useful to go back and forth like this.
This is big, guys.
Being able to do this has changed everything.
My God.
Also, I need to put my money in the thingy first.
Let's see here.
Potions that I need for the fight.
I need... Let's do... one of these.
And one of these.
One of these.
Let's do... Yeah, let's bring the strange brew.
And what else?
Maybe this one is actually not too bad.
Because there's going to be lifehards during the fight and I'm too busy jumping around and doing things to actually go for them a lot of the time.
I wonder how big of an effect that is.
Let's try it.
And then we can sort them like that.
Let's just get that beautiful.
Okay.
In fact, I want to try a bee nade against the bee.
Probably not going to work too well, but who knows.
You know what else?
I'm taking one sunflower with me.
I'm not sure they can plant it down there, but God dang it.
I'm going to try it.
Let's go.
Hold on.
What's up, guys?
Okay, fine.
All right, take me down.
Take me.
Ah, shit.
Right.
I'm stuck here, of course.
Aha!
Smart.
See that?
That's actually... You can make a cool shortcut like that using that liquid.
It's not a terrible idea, is it?
Feels like a genius idea.
Man, I felt so smart when I figured out where my stars were by looking at where they went when I sorted or when I played the auto sword thingy.
God, I felt good, you know?
And I'm here, actually.
It's right here.
Put some lights.
Yeah, this looks pretty cool, actually.
Let's see if I can put this flower here.
Oh, wait, that's not the flower.
Oh, it is.
Oh, I figured.
I figured.
It needs dirt.
I wonder, though, if I brought dirt here, if I put it down, if it would have worked.
Cool thing to try, I guess.
Wait a minute.
This is consumable.
Oh, I know why.
I thought I could just eat it.
All right, potions, heart reach, blood, iron skin.
We need magic power and thorns.
Benates, equip them.
I'm actually excited for this.
Nice.
I think everything is ready to go.
There's nothing else that needs to be done.
Let's do it.
Let's start the day off with a good old fight.
Hey, Nate.
Are they doing anything or are they friends with the... Oh, they're working.
Look at that.
Oh, that is working beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
He's going to do the charge now, I think.
Do it.
Charge me.
There it is.
Ah, I was a bit too slow there.
There we go.
Okay, yeah.
Come on, he's not going to do it again.
All right.
Oh, man, we're doing well.
This is easy.
Holy shit.
Okay, I got lucky there.
Give me a crit, a nice crit.
Dude, I'm killing this.
Look at this.
I'm a goddamn pro.
He's doing that now.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I'm getting my ass kicked.
I'm getting my ass kicked.
There we go.
Look at that.
Wasn't that smooth or what?
Thank you.
A treasure bag.
Let's see what's in it.
Wait.
Oh, right click, of course.
Another hurtful beekeeper.
A bee shirt.
Oh, do I always get the same items?
I've been noticing this with the other goodie bags from the other bosses.
You seem to always get the same items, except maybe be sure it is new here.
But like this is these three are the same.
Fashion statement.
Equip armor or vanity clothing in all three social slots.
Cool.
Let's see here.
Do I just put this anywhere?
I mean, that's kind of cool, I guess, actually.
Oh, no, no, wait, it consumes hot.
What is the point?
Why can't I just do this?
Oh, because I can't.
Okay, fine.
That makes a lot of sense, actually.
That's why I can't, because you can't.
There, explanation.
That's amazing.
Get up there.
Give me that little thingy.
Thank you.
All right.
We got more bee wax, though, so we can craft items now.
In fact, I'm going to click on a button.
This button right here goes back immediately.
Feels good.
Okay.
I already have a bee outfit on right now.
Wait, do I have bee wings behind me?
What is that?
On the outfit there, look at that.
That looks like I have a bee backpack.
A bee pack.
Or maybe it's wings.
I don't know what it is.
Okay.
Let's see.
Crafting.
Is it here?
It is here.
Let's see.
I can make a hornet staff.
Hold on.
Before I do this, wasn't there a way to see?
Could I make another one of those that can summon the bee?
How did I make... How did I actually get those before?
I kind of forgot about that.
Wait a minute.
Bradley?
Quickly tell me... Okay, it wasn't this one.
Was it the honey block?
Honey block.
Was it this one that I used to make it?
Or did I find it?
I don't remember.
No, it was this one.
Stinger, hive, and bottled honey.
Oh, I can... Oh, no problem.
I can keep doing this.
Alright, cool.
Well, that's good to know.
Very good to know.
Let me make the gear.
Headgear?
Oh, what's happening here?
How dare you?
Who didn't close the door?
Probably was me.
Oh, I thought that was an enemy.
Alright, that's one then.
Let's do the others.
Breastplate.
And boots.
And now I want to see if there's a set bonus here.
Wait, why?
Oh, of course, it's not a helmet.
I'm done, I'm done.
Let's see here.
It says...
What does it say now?
Increases summon damage by 10%.
Cool.
Alright.
So that's a lot in total.
Not bad at all.
And now, do I have enough for the final thing?
I don't think I do.
I need to craft more of the... I need to kill another bee, actually.
Let's see.
I need stinger.
And let's see if I remember this.
I need... honey... I need bottled honey.
I have that, I believe.
Is it on me?
It's on me.
And the last part I kind of forgot.
I can make it, though.
Let's make two of them.
We still have all the buffs, by the way.
Let's just quickly go back.
Let's go back and utilize this while it still lasts.
Here we go.
Go here.
Fall into this liquid.
Wait, why is this here again?
That was so weird.
Come on.
Hurray.
Go this way.
I'm slowly becoming a bee.
Okay.
Go.
Oh, wait.
Put this up first.
Didn't I take the thing hanging from the... There we go.
Let's put it in the center.
I don't know if it'll reach all the way.
There we go.
And go.
Here we go again.
Okay, he's coming quick.
He's doing this.
Can't catch me.
Oh, wait.
I don't have enough... I just realized my mistake.
I have the wrong set on.
It's a mistake!
That's why I'm doing so little damage.
I'm taking a lot of damage here.
Oh, God.
Come on.
I got lucky there.
Okay.
Oh, I'm taking lots of damage.
Ah, shit.
Here we go.
Oh!
Oi!
That was close.
I'm taking way too much damage.
Beanade!
Get him, bees!
Kill your queen!
Oh, my God.
It's fine.
We're totally chilling.
Come on.
There we go.
That was kind of hard when you didn't have infinite mana there.
I realized my mistake a little too late.
Okay.
Let's quickly equip this again for now.
Let's see what we get.
Ah!
You do get some new stuff.
It is a little bit different every time.
Just a little bit.
We got some more beeswax.
Okay, let's do one more.
Potions have worn off, but I think we can do it without.
Maybe I'll even try this.
No, no, no, no.
Wait.
Forceful beekeeper.
Hmm.
You know what?
Let me also unequip this.
I just realized.
Maybe it's better to have this one.
Or even.
Nah, that's fine.
That's good.
Let's go one more.
We are killing things.
Oh, shit.
The bee nades.
There's bees everywhere.
Peace!
Oprah style.
Oh, I just did a lot of damage there.
Come on.
Come on, get him.
Summons.
Dance, dance.
Bob and weave.
Oh, I'm killing this.
Look at this.
Okay, you're doing that.
Oh, wait, there's two of them.
What?
What's happening?
Why?
Why do we have two of them?
Huh?
Alright, it's getting crazier.
Ah, I think I'm dead.
There's no way I can win.
No!
What the fuck?
Are you kidding me?
Why were the two of them?
What?
I dropped one plats in them.
Hopefully I can get all that back.
Oh, my God.
I'm God.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
This better fucking be there when I get back.
That money better be there.
Or I will go ballistic.
Come on.
Why would that?
Why was that happening?
What did I do just now?
Maybe the, you know what?
Maybe the original beat just respawns after a while and it just happened so happened while I was doing this.
Where's the rest of my money?
Where's my money, bitch?
No.
Where is it?
Did it fall down here?
Do I have to go venturing in the... What?
It's fucking gone.
Bro.
Motherfucker.
Alright, well.
Now I don't, ah, now I don't even have the B thing anymore.
So I can't even summon it.
You know what?
That's fine.
I'm gonna go back anyway.
Whatever.
It's time to craft the ultimate item.
When I say the ultimate, I mean the last.
There's one more.
The Hornet Staff.
Okay.
So hold on now.
This has 12 summon damage now.
But this, oh wait a minute, this one, where is it?
Increases the strength of friendly bees.
If I put that on, it still says 12.
So I think it's only relating to the bee nade.
Unfortunately.
Uh, let's see here.
Okay, we got one.
Can I make two of them here as well?
Yes.
But hold on, wasn't there... Let me equip this now.
Hey, I got three of them now.
Four?
So yeah, this doubles it.
My god!
Okay, okay, hold on.
Now this has 14 because I have better summon damage, right?
Dude, let's try this out.
Come on.
Oh fuck.
No, I need to go to the pylon.
Let's go.
Uh,
do I want to... Nah, I don't think I want to kill it one more time.
You know what, I'm just going to rock it like this and see what happens.
So this is nice.
And you know what the best thing is?
I can do all of this while still using my magic missile.
Or actually, even this.
Oh yeah, right, right, right, right.
This one is probably going to summon things that will deal more damage because I have the rash hive pack on.
So I'm going to be slashing things, dude.
And then when I feel like it, I will switch over and use my... Where is it?
Magic missile.
I'm just going to do that.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
And then when I'm out of mana, I switch to melee and I go, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup, cup.
And I summon bees.
Bees everywhere!
Alright, perfect.
That's my current setup.
Let's just roll with that for a while.
Test it out.
See how it goes.
That seems fun.
Now, you.
Will you buy some things?
You can have one of these because I have two of them already.
In fact, I have three of them.
I guess I can also sell these because I have three of them.
Hold on, what do I want?
Melee speed?
Damage or movement?
Maybe I want damage.
I mean, 1% it's not really a lot, but you know, it's fine.
And I have two of these already, so let me get rid of that.
I have bee pants, bee shirt.
I don't have a bee head yet.
Maybe I do want to keep killing the bee until I get the bee head as well.
Is that a little crazy?
Oh, by the way, I think I used the strange brew during the fight because I only have one left.
It was used.
OK, let's do that.
And now we click on the magic button.
Everything goes in.
The armor stuff.
I also have all this.
Sure.
This stays here, of course.
Put this in here.
Another honey block.
Let's put that in.
Let's put it in miscellaneous.
And the bottled honey can go in potions.
And this one is definitely also a specialized thingy.
It goes in miscellaneous.
One flower.
Let me just put it down here.
There we go.
Beautiful stuff.
I also forgot to bring my heart lantern.
I'm downstairs, unfortunately.
Stinger in.
Live crystal.
Put it in miscellaneous.
All right, bee nades.
Let's take some more platforms with us.
It's good to have.
Do I have any wood?
Hold on, let's do the trick again.
Do that and then... OK, so I don't have any more here.
Perfect.
Good to know.
You know what would be a nice little quality of life thing?
If you mouse over this and it says 16 and then it could say comma and another number and the other number would be how many you have in storage.
Similar to how Dark Souls does it.
That would be kind of neat.
Just so you know whether or not you should even try and look for them in the chests, you know.
It would be kind of cool.
Maybe if you control click it, it will highlight the chest where it's in.
It will bleep or blop or doff, you know.
It'll do a thing.
Something.
Acorns, delete that shit.
Mushroom, eat that shit.
Now the wood, turn it into platforms.
All of it.
Yo!
There.
Beautiful.
Also do this.
Oh, and also the B-wax and the fallen stars.
Fallen stars go here.
Let's sell those.
The B-wax goes in miscellaneous.
Yikes.
Crate potion.
I'll keep it on me.
I'm in here.
All right.
What's the next?
What's the next thing that I want to do?
So hold on.
I killed a boss now in the jungle.
Which will get the attention of someone.
Bradley, can you remind me about that?
Let's see.
Oh yeah, the snow biome.
There was also something going on there if there's bad weather in the night.
I gotta go check that out.
Marble, granite, jungle, if you're willing to dig deep enough.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Man, what did you... Oh yeah, here.
In the middle of the night on snowy evenings.
A terrifying roaring sound comes from the wilderness.
Something is out there.
Middle of the night.
Okay.
Next time it's snowy, I was about to say.
Or raining, I guess, because that's snow when you're in the snowy region.
I'm gonna go there.
Tell me about the other thing you said.
About the... Oh, maybe he doesn't say it anymore, because I already did it.
Yeah.
Okay, so I already did that.
But didn't he say to get the attention of the lizard people or something?
I needed to do that.
Maybe that's what it took.
Maybe I can now go here.
I'm gonna try that now.
Go to... I guess we have a bit of walking to do, but we can do fishing on the way.
Or can we?
Do I have bait?
I have now.
That's good enough for me.
Go here.
Man, look at this little house.
Isn't that fucking fantastic?
I love how this looks.
I just made a hole in the floor.
It's okay.
It is what it is.
Did I bring my fishing rod at all?
Fuck!
Alright, that's fine.
Let's do this for now.
Man, look at my entourage here.
Hey, kill him!
I mean, they're kind of useless.
They kind of miss half the time.
Come on.
Guys.
Okay, it's not bad.
I mean, it's definitely nice for crowd control, I guess.
Taking care of little annoying enemies.
You know?
Question is, though.
Question is, is it gonna be...
Is it gonna be enough of a increase to exchange the infinite mana situation?
That's the question.
Oh wait, I guess I was gonna have this.
I'm gonna try that.
Let me try and kill some enemies with this.
With the sword.
Hey!
I am the bee man.
Fear me.
I should turn you into bees and coordinates.
All the flying insects.
Hey!
Gah!
Wait, what did it say again?
Wait.
Summon killer bees after... Oh, really?
Are they like the small ones?
The same like comes from the bee nade?
Because I didn't notice it just now.
Maybe that's what happened.
And it's whenever you strike a foe.
Okay.
Interesting.
Wait, am I... where am I going?
I'm on the way.
I am on the way.
To glory and success.
Come here!
Hey!
Killer bees!
Did it happen?
I can't see if it happened or not.
Maybe I'm blind.
I am not noticing it.
Also, I want to equip this again.
Because bees... Did I see a little bee?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're definitely there.
I see him.
I just wonder how much damage they actually do.
Look, it flew off in that direction now.
Alright.
How far?
We're here.
Now we go down.
Look at that.
A little workbench.
I wonder who did that.
It wasn't me.
What?
Killer bees!
Actually, they're not too bad.
That's kind of cool.
Also, I haven't been doing any melee.
Sorry.
Melee?
Melee day?
I haven't done any of that in a while.
Oh, yeah?
You want to be me?
I'll be you.
Grab me axes into your domain.
Look at that.
It has a little icon with some kind of Aztec rune looking thing.
It's like I definitely need a key.
Look at the keyhole.
I need to find a key or some kind of object that fits in that hole that I can then twist and turn until it's done.
Okay, so I can't get in there yet.
Fuck!
Maybe I'll go back down again and try my hand at the wall of flesh and lack beetle.
Hold on.
What's that?
Hey, you!
Oh, wait.
You're a killable.
Okay.
Right.
You just gave me a violent something?
A husk.
Right.
Oh, a violent husk.
Not a violent husk.
A lot of things in this game are violent.
What can I say?
There'll be like a... Oh, here's a depth meter.
It'll tell you how deep you go, but this one's violent.
Okay.
Fuck people up.
It's the most unexpected thing ever.
Okay.
I want to go.
Where do I want to go?
I also want to go back here at some point.
Oh, yeah.
I was going to try and make a house in that cave over there because maybe the old man will arrive.
He likes to be in that spot, right?
According to the bestiary.
So let me open my inventory and do it.
And then I will actually just go down here again, I think.
But first, we're going to need some supplies.
If I'm going to face that monster down there, we're going to need a world of items.
Put all that shit in there.
I never did go fishing, did I?
Because I didn't have my rod.
That's okay.
Maybe I do have it.
Do I have it?
No, I don't.
But, yeah.
You know what?
I'm going to bring my other outfit as well, just in case.
Where did I put it?
Did I put it here?
No.
Yeah, no.
Wait, where did I put it?
Where did I put it?
Oh, that's like the one thing I hate about this.
Like the inventory management is terrible.
Fuck!
Like, it's gone.
It's gone from the face of the earth.
There it is.
I don't want to equip it yet.
I just want to have it on me in case I need it.
All right, good.
Potions.
I want iron skin.
I want magic power.
I also want... I want... What do I want?
I wonder if honey is better than potions.
How natural are we talking?
How much?
How good is this?
That's the question I have right now.
Let's take these.
And let's... This is only on water.
It's not going to work on lava.
Let's do this one.
And maybe this is also okay.
I need this for sure.
Obsidian skin.
And then I think I'm good.
In fact, I'll make some potions myself.
Let me see what I can make.
Remind me again.
Okay, let's see here.
Wait a minute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, I thought it was new.
It's not.
Fishing power, thorns.
Is there anything I absolutely need for this fight?
Maybe mana regeneration.
For my magic missile.
Star, daybloom, moon glow.
Let's just grab them.
Stars here.
Daybloom there.
Moon glow there, man.
That was quick.
Wow.
I impressed myself.
Let's just make it immediately before we forget.
Make two of them.
Thank you.
Next.
Show me what else I can do with this bottle of water.
Secrets.
Oh, this.
Wow.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Blink rooted cactus.
Bro.
Hey.
Oh, oh, I can make it.
Hallelujah.
Make three of these bad boys.
Wow.
Actually, I want to make more, but I need water, so let's go grab the empty bottles.
Let's actually go fill up empty bottles here.
Where's my empty bottles?
Mission.
Okay, here we go again.
Let's go find the empty bottles.
That's probably not there, is it?
Are they in here?
Can I blind?
Oh, did I use them all on the honey?
I probably did.
Fuck.
Well.
Glass.
Remind me how to make those again.
Empty bottles.
Bradley.
Glass.
Oh, there.
Bottle.
Furnace.
Right.
That makes sense.
Make a bunch of these.
14 sounds about good.
I wonder if this will work down here.
Is this enough?
Doesn't look like it.
Hold on.
We've got to find a more substantial body of water here.
There's water down here.
There we go.
Beautiful stuff.
Stag them up.
And here we go.
Let's see, what else should I make?
So I made three swiftness potions.
Dude, I use those all the time back in classic to form BRD as a mage.
That was the thing you needed to do the pull where you pulled like the whole first room and then AOE'd it down.
Actually, maybe this was on Nostellarius before that.
I don't remember.
It's been a while.
But those were the times, man.
Let's see, what else did I need?
I need to talk to the guy.
Give him the water, damn it.
Feather Falls, Belonkur.
No.
Hey, get out of here.
Oh, greater healing.
Oh, but I need Crystal Shard.
I don't have that.
Rip.
Yeah, I don't know how to get that.
I'll find out later.
What's this?
Flask of Gold.
Oh, no.
Titan Potion, Dangerous could be... you know what?
The Flipper Potion could be nice.
Water Leaf and Shiverthorn.
Water Leaf.
Where are you at?
One Shiverthorn.
Oh, that's...
that's not a lot, is it?
But it... I'm hoping that also means lava.
So I can move.
If I fall in, I can quickly get out again.
Seems good to me.
Flipper time!
You know I love to flip.
Love flipping.
Wait, why did my Shiverthorn get used?
Didn't I just use that?
Maybe I didn't.
Alright, take the bottled water.
Is there anything else?
Let's see.
Oh, also this one.
I wonder what happens if I use this during the fight?
Oh!
Oh, wait, I don't have this.
You know what?
I think I know where to get it.
We gotta go fish in the Crimson area.
100%, that's how you get it.
Let me actually try that.
We're gonna do that right now.
Fishing Rod.
I saw you here.
No, I saw you there.
No, where did I see you?
Where did I see you?
Fishing Rod.
Fishing Rod?
Oh, it's in the fishing probably.
No, it's not.
There it is.
Nice.
Bait.
Almost left without the bait.
There we go.
Let's do it.
Hop, hop, hop.
Get up here and then do that.
Go on the highway.
And then we're gonna go here.
Find some... Down there maybe actually.
Jump!
Alright, give me that star.
Oh, I'm taking damage here.
Oh, maybe this is the liquid I need to, but this is probably not a big enough pool.
Let me try it.
Not that one.
Let's go there.
It's probably not gonna work.
Nah, it's not.
We gotta find a bigger one.
I wonder if it's the depth or the size and width that matters here.
Or maybe it's just the volume in general.
Okay, this one's not working either.
This one.
100%.
Put it there.
Wait a minute.
Deathweed, nice.
Alright, bring it on.
Flounder.
Oh, this is so nice.
Fishing with the bees is actually big.
Because I can just chill and fish while the bees take care of everything.
That's lovely.
Big fan of that.
Crimson tigerfish.
I look so silly.
I look like a little kid at Halloween with his bee costume on.
Kinda cute.
Man, so many crimson tigerfish.
Also, my inventory is about to runneth over, as they say.
Let me actually quickly put a bunch of non-essentials in here.
Let's put this in here as well, and this, and money, of course.
And that's it.
Keep fishing.
That was a long throw.
Is it called a throw?
A long... You know what I mean.
A long throw, yeah.
That makes sense.
Come on, this has got to be the place for the Eben koi.
Or the Eben koi.
I don't know how to pronounce it, actually.
Is it Eben or Eben?
I don't know.
It broke.
I'm aiming down, but it still sort of throws it.
Oh, okay.
Never mind.
I think I understand now.
Also, do I only have three bees?
Guys?
Where's the last bee?
Oh, it's up here.
Never mind.
By the way, speaking of summons here, can I do both?
No, it replaces.
Fuck!
So there's three bees now and one of those guys.
You know what?
Maybe that's fine.
Actually, I can still take it back.
Yeah!
Awesome.
I thought for a second I had to go back and click on the thing at first.
Himo piranha.
That's a bloodfish.
Ironcra... Oh, nice.
Let's see.
Tungsten?
Uh, ooh.
Let's just use all our bait.
Man, these things are numerous.
Gingerbeard!
Huh?
Wait, where does it go?
Oh, it's down here.
What the fuck?
Look at this!
I now have a gingerbeard.
That's amazing.
Lounder.
How many do I have left?
This is my last bait, I think.
Oh, no, I don't have any bait.
That's it.
I done used it all.
Alright, well, I tried.
Didn't work.
I guess I'm just gonna go over here now and go straight down.
So, let's go back up again.
Let's go back up over here.
Da-ba-boom.
I'll go up here like that.
Yeah, go this way.
Give me this.
I'll go at it.
There we are.
So, what do I have equipped by now?
I have the hive pack on.
I'm gonna be being so hard.
The question is, though, this sword is gonna be shit against the wall of flesh.
Because I don't wanna be close to it at all.
I wanna be as far away as I possibly can.
So, yeah, I don't think that's gonna happen.
So, actually, yeah, maybe I'll just... How fast do I go oom?
Let's see.
How long do I wait?
Oh, that's quite a while, isn't it?
Actually, it's not too bad.
I can shoot a lot, then focus on running.
Then shoot a lot, focus on running.
It's not too bad.
That can work, I think.
Alright, go.
And then I have my summons to help me with all the adds that are getting spawned.
Oh, wait a minute!
I need something before I go down.
Oh, I... I was about to say.
I need my... I need the doll.
Otherwise, I won't get anywhere.
There we go.
This is my last attempt, it seems.
Where did I find them again?
Were they just drops from enemies?
Maybe I just keep killing things down there and eventually I'll find more.
Yeah, that seems good.
Let's just do that.
Alright.
And here we are.
Look at my bees, or my hornets, I should say.
Fighting for me.
Descendant to the underworld.
Look at my turtle.
It's not helicopter status.
That's very interesting to me.
Why that is.
Whoa!
Why is... Hold on, this looks interesting, doesn't it?
What is that?
Oh, why is this this color?
Wait a minute.
Why is this special?
Actually, there is something here I want to take.
Okay, so let me try that and let me switch.
Oh, it's definitely faster with these.
Yeah.
On some blocks, the molten one is better.
I think my void pack just now was being used.
I'm burning.
Excuse me.
Oh, I need my obsidian.
Potion on as well.
Well, not yet.
Let's just chill for a second.
Let's see how effective these are.
If I just traverse the area, will you kill things at a decent pace here?
What are we talking?
It's kind of bad.
They're kind of terrible, I gotta admit.
They're not that great, are they?
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
Then again, if they end up shooting at the wall of flesh, like you can't really miss.
Right?
So maybe that's a nice constant source of damage in the end.
In any case, I gotta go take a piss before I start this.
So, let's pause.
I'll be right back.
See ya.
Alright, here we go.
So, a thing I want to test now is obsidian potion with the flipper.
See if there's a difference.
Also, there's a guide on here.
Let me be you.
Wow, I took a shit ton of damage there.
You don't want to be in melee when he does that attack.
Wow.
Alright, let's just chill for a second here.
Obsidian lasts a long time, right?
Yeah, 6 minutes.
Drink one of these.
Okay, quickly check out lava.
Okay, it's like very sluggish, right?
Now?
With the flipper?
Oh yeah!
Much better!
Fuck yeah!
Okay, perfect!
Back up here.
Let's just regen a little bit.
Let's do this one.
That one.
This one.
And one of these.
One of that.
This one.
And I think we're about ready.
Do we want to change anything else before I go here?
You know what?
Maybe I'll change that one.
That one kind of sucks.
Because I'm not going to be spawning many bees here.
I'm not going to go in with my hurtful beekeeper.
In fact, I will not use it at all, I don't think.
I'm going to go with my sapinator and then just hope the bees are going to do their job.
Or the hornets, sorry.
Swiftness potion.
There we go.
And these all stack.
Look at that.
Oh my god.
That's insane.
Delete that, delete mud.
And I think we're ready!
Maybe I need speed.
So, this one.
That's better.
Okay.
It's time.
And then I also have a beanade, I guess, that I can use.
Whoops.
In fact, maybe the beanades will be really good.
I don't know.
Hell butterfly.
Alright, I think it's time.
Let's just go for it, huh?
Let me zoom out a bit.
Do I want to zoom out?
Like that.
Here we go.
Okay,
focus now.
Focus, focus, focus.
Okay, keep running a bit more.
Come on, kill him.
We're doing decent damage so far.
I mean, this is a long stretch of nothing, so be careful.
Let's try and dodge those attacks he does.
Okay, he's coming now, so we go again.
Come on, go.
Inside, inside the door, come on.
Jump here.
Nice.
And go like this.
Keep shooting while we do this.
Let's be optimal here.
He's shooting lasers, so we dodge that.
Dodge the lasers.
Sick dodges, look at that.
Oh, but we have flipper potion.
Everything's fine.
We'll be flivering.
Get up there.
Oh, shit.
Man, flipper potion is the tits.
Oh, yeah, it's so good.
It's a game changer.
Come on, bees, shoot, shoot.
Okay, keep going, keep going.
Yeah, yeah, keep moving, keep moving.
Also, he starts to increase in speed at some point.
I've got to be careful there.
Okay, go.
There we go.
Okay, nice.
We have a little bridge here, actually.
Okay, I healed up a little bit there.
Nice, nice.
Okay, half health.
Keep it going.
Is that the point at which he starts to move faster?
Keep attacking.
Keep moving, keep moving.
Okay, go, go, go.
Come on.
Keep shooting.
Oh, he's coming quick now.
He's coming quick.
You see this?
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
I'm scared.
Oh, it's coming quick.
Oh, I think I'm going to die here.
I got to focus on running right now.
Oh, no, flipper potion to the rescue.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Just go, mine it.
Heal, nice.
Okay, I haven't gone this far to the right before.
Okay, keep going.
Nice.
Nice, I got a bunch of momentum there.
Nice, nice.
I'm low on HP here, though.
Oh my god.
Come on.
Oh, I'm almost dead.
I'm burning.
What?
Did I not have my obsidian on me anymore?
Bro, this guy is so fucking hard.
Jesus.
Oh my god.
How the fuck, man?
How am I going to kill this dude?
Shit.
Also, I just realized I wasn't planning on having this gear on.
Fuck.
I was noticing why I couldn't keep shooting my gun.
I wasn't planning on having this on.
I was planning on having bees, but then use my normal sapper.
I got a forceful bat-bat somehow.
Maybe I could bat some bats with this.
Cool.
May heal user on hit.
That's cool.
Not bad.
I also forgot to try on the bee nades.
Ah, shit.
We can't try anymore, though, because actually we can try and find another doll, I guess.
It's not the other world.
You know what?
I'm going to go back down.
I'm going to make it my goddamn mission to fuck this guy up.
I don't care anymore.
It's time to just kill him.
I've had enough of his shenanigans.
There.
Put my gear on again, please.
Honestly, I don't know about the Oprah build.
The Oprah build is not really working for me.
I don't want to represent the bees, either.
Let's get rid of that.
I do want the ginger beard, though.
Ginger beard stays.
Now the bee pants and all that goes in here.
I have ninja pants.
Don't want that.
Space gun is definitely better, I think.
But the problem is with the space gun, you know what?
I need something quickly to clear AOE.
Like, crowd control here.
So I'm shooting my sapper, right?
I go, pew, pew, pew.
And I attack the boss.
But then I also need something to just clean out all the ads.
And I think the magic missile is there for me for that.
You know?
And I don't need to do that all the time.
While I'm not using it, it regenerates my mana while I pew, pew, pew, you know?
So I think it's good.
I think it's good.
You go in there.
The bee stuff.
Let's put that in here.
And let's... Let's use... You know what?
Fuck the bees.
The bees suck.
The horn staff is terrible.
I want the unpleasant imp staff.
I want these.
Yes, sir.
Two of these seem just as good, honestly.
Hellbat banner.
Alright, let's just try again.
Let's go down there and see if we can't find another doll.
Did I remember... Is there anything I forgot?
Hold on.
Let me see if there's anything I need.
Let's think.
Let's look at the weapons.
What do I have?
I don't think I want to use anything else.
I could try... You know what?
I could try the star cannon.
But it's like... kind of terrible.
Have I tried shooting this?
Yeah.
It's like the same damage as my sapper.
It's kind of terrible now.
And I'll be using all my stars.
That's... I don't know about that, man.
It's like a terrible idea.
Alright.
Go back down!
I think we have everything we need for now.
I think the thing we need most is just practice.
Practice makes perfect, as they say.
And you know what?
Maybe I'll even go further to the left first before I start, so I have more room.
I died all the way over there and the boss was like... Was he at like 30% or something when I died?
So I definitely need more room.
Is it raining blood?
Oh, by the way, speaking of rainy weather.
Let's try and go to the icy region.
Also, what is the time?
10.10 PM.
Is it night yet?
Look at my outfit.
A real gentleman with the raincoat.
Isn't this perfect for this right now, by the way?
It's raining and I have my raincoat on.
That's fantastic.
Alright, I'm gonna go this way.
Let's go to the icy region.
In fact, take the high-speed rail here.
Into rail.
Oh, it's right here, never mind.
Oh yeah, it's a storm.
What's the time?
It's night now, though.
Hold on, I forgot what he said.
Maybe we need to dig.
Oh, I can't see shit.
That's water.
Go to the left.
Oh my god.
Look at the effect here.
It's actually kind of crazy.
I even made a long way down here, actually.
Hey, sir.
Get out of my way.
Oh, you know what I want to do?
I want to try and fish here.
Maybe something will happen during this weather.
And my, at least my minions are going to protect me while I fish.
Maybe something special will happen just now.
Oh wait, I don't have bait!
No!
Oh, wait, I got a snow coat.
Oh.
Let's put that on in this weather.
Demon eye.
Alright, let's try and go down.
Come on.
Oh!
Deer tops!
What the?
Here we go.
Deer tops has awoken.
The fuck is a deer top?
Sir?
Deer top?
Oh wait, I should probably...
What's up?
Oh, he has a hand.
Oh!
Okay.
Shoot him.
Okay, he does some kind of AOE shit.
Oh, he's stuck, he's stuck.
Okay, we gotta dodge that.
That's not too hard.
Am I doing any damage here?
It seems like I'm not doing very much.
Oh!
Come on!
I need Flipper Potion!
Oh, I'm slowed!
Oh!
Get out of there!
Okay, just keep jumping when he does that.
Oh my god.
Okay, okay, holy shit.
Jesus!
I got murked by debris!
What?
What does that mean?
God damn.
Fucking deer top, man.
Alright, can I go back there and fuck you up?
We ain't finished, you and I.
You hear me?
Come on.
Oh, he's still there, I think.
Oh, deer clops!
Oh!
It's the one-eyed man!
Dude!
We have a one-eyed man here.
Hold on.
Magic power, swiftness, hunter, sure.
Ah!
Can I just stay on the rail?
Deer clops!
I'm staying on the rail, dude.
What's he gonna do?
What's he gonna do about it?
Is he taking damage?
Wait, can I sort of aim in the direction he's approximately at?
Oh, it doesn't work like that, I don't think.
Oh, crap.
But I can just go up there whenever I want, right?
Oh!
Oh, no, I'm dead.
Yeah, I definitely gotta dodge that every time.
Oh, he still has low HP from last time.
Oh, that was sick.
Come on, get out of there.
Dodge.
Oh, I can't see shit.
Okay, he's kinda low HP.
We gotta hurry back.
Come on.
Hurry.
We can make it.
We just gotta hurry up real fast now.
Go, it's still raining.
Hurry!
Come on.
Oh, we're so slow.
Oh, he's there, he's there.
He's kinda weird that I can just go back and keep attacking him, but whatever.
I'll take it, man.
I'll take it.
Come on.
Fast, fast, fast, fast.
Maybe he'll despawn when the rain stops.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
I got him now.
I got him for sure.
Let's go.
Let's not get too overeager here.
Yeah!
Haha!
Gotcha!
Gotcha, bitch!
Shiverthorn seeds, snow pants, and treasure bag.
Deerclops.
Ooh.
Deerclops mask.
Hey!
Radio thing!
Allows the user to see the world differently.
What?
Say what now?
Get away from me.
And then we have a houndio shootios.
24 summon damage.
Summon's a sentry.
Summon's an arcane... Get away from me.
Summon's an arcane construct to shoot optic blasts at your enemies.
Well, that's pretty good!
It's the eye of the one-eyed man.
But not as good as my magic missile.
That thing slaps.
The magic missile, people.
You heard it here first.
The best weapon in the game.
Look at the icon now!
The icon is different because I have this mask on.
And what do you mean?
Wait, is the world different?
Yeah, it is!
It's like more black and white.
What the hell?
Let's try and go back.
Yo, what the f... Does this work here?
I think so?
Wait a minute.
Yeah!
Forbidden knowledge.
Ooh, wow.
Dude!
This is kind of scary.
What am I seeing that I'm not... Kibodo!
Who the fuck are you?
Lightning casts powerful shadows.
Shadows cast powerful lightning.
Okay.
Imbuing station.
Used to craft weapon-imbuement flasks.
Thank you.
I will use that.
We have a pure water fountain.
Wait, I wonder if I can use this to fill up my empty bottles.
Wait.
Corrupt water fountain.
Water fountain.
Flow gun.
Allows the collection of seeds for ammo.
Oh!
Okay.
Romeo has arrived.
Hold on.
Fuck you, Kibodo.
I wanna talk to Romeo.
Romeo?
Oh, he's there now.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold on now.
Romeo?
What's up, man?
I like that he went here.
I would do the same.
Hurry up and buy!
Okay, okay, okay, I will.
I will.
A star hairpin winter cape.
Ultra bright torch.
Really?
Oh, yeah!
That is an... Oh!
Precise bone helm.
Summon shadow hands to attack your foes.
I've got a headache just looking at it.
Oh, but wait, it's... Wait, can I put it here?
Oh, yeah!
Okay, okay, now we're talking.
Okay, let's try that out.
I kind of missed that.
And the houndier shoot you.
So funny.
It's not a material, unfortunately.
Oh, well, oh, yeah, right, this one.
Let's put that here, I guess.
Remove that.
So, how do I do this?
Free shipping?
Oh, I'm talking to him.
Katana.
Chalice.
I wonder if I can use that to go into a dungeon.
The dazzled nectar.
Sunshine of Israponi.
You know what?
I need the sunshine of Israponi in my life, because it goes in this house.
Oh, it's way too big!
Okay, it's not gonna go in this house.
It's gonna go somewhere else.
Weapon embumement.
Hold on, what does it say again?
Used to craft weapon embumement flasks.
So, I wonder if I need a flask.
Hold on.
Put it here.
Let's go back here now.
Let's do... let's get some empty bottles.
Maybe that will do it.
Oh, I don't have any.
Can I empty this?
Oh, no.
Wait.
Dude!
The water restores life!
No cooldown!
Oh, nevermind.
Oh.
Okay, nevermind, nevermind, nevermind, nevermind.
Jesus.
Fuck, I'm sorry.
I thought I just discovered the ultimate trick here.
God damn it.
Okay, okay, okay.
We need to find some glass, so we need sand.
Do we have sand?
Let's see.
Construction.
Sand.
Sort.
Sandstone.
Slap.
I don't know, I don't know.
Probably.
Sandlock.
That's gotta do it.
Look at how the world looks now.
I do wonder if this has any effect on the... I wonder if I can only see this guy.
Hold on.
Why am I not just testing it?
No, he's still here.
Nevermind.
Hold on, let me see if there's a difference.
Let me try and really look.
Wait, why can't I now... Oh, it's the wrong one.
Where is it?
There.
Magic radio thing.
I don't immediately see a difference.
Wait, who's Seth?
Bradley is dead.
Of course.
Right.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
It makes sense.
All right.
Cool.
Well, the plan was to go downstairs, so I'm gonna do that again.
And I'm gonna test all these new items I have, I guess.
The houndier shooters.
Let's do this.
One of these.
Do I have two?
Wait, it doesn't...
Where did my weapon go?
Oh!
Why can I only have one?
Huh?
Hold on, am I blind?
Are there two right now?
Hello?
Where'd he go?
Oh, wait a minute!
Okay, it's a... I get it, it's a turret.
It stays in... Okay, okay.
Nevermind.
Okay.
I see.
I thought it was a floating eye.
Goddamn.
I got bamboozled just now.
All right, we're back to the unpleasant imp staff.
I guess I can put this down, but it's kind of...
It's kind of useless, because I keep running away from it.
So, whatever.
All right, I wanted to do a glass.
It's glass time.
And lots of it.
Just do all that.
And then it's time to make some bottles.
That's fine.
And then...
I'm gonna experiment with the imbuing station.
Let's try and place that there.
And can I do anything now?
Maybe it needs to be filled with water.
Let me fill a little... No, wait, I have water already.
Can I craft a flask?
Is that at all possible?
Hold on, let me put the glass inside Seth.
Seth?
It's glass time.
Let's see.
Anything glassy?
Oh, that actually looks kind of neat.
Yo, this is kind of neat.
I want to make this stuff.
Pretty nice.
Martian astro clock!
I want to make that.
Dude, I know how my home is going to look now.
It's going to be all glass.
Mug, wine glass...
Lab post.
Mmm, dude.
The glass, I've been sleeping on the glass.
Wait, I have to make a terrarium.
Also because it's a material.
We gotta try.
I need furnace.
We can't not make a terrarium in terraria.
Okay, Seth?
Look at this terrarium I made.
Oh, of course.
Putting things inside.
That makes a lot of sense, actually.
Can I do any of that right now?
By the way, don't I have a bunny?
What about this?
Will that work?
A seagull cage!
Dude, it's massive!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh, alright.
Hold on.
Go up here.
Construction.
Let's also click this button.
Everything goes in.
And nothing comes back.
You can't explain that.
Let's go to Desert Pylon.
And while we're here, we need to...
Dammit!
What did I want to do just now?
Right.
The cage.
Seagull.
Let's...
There!
Kind of mean.
A seagull needs to fly around.
But that goes there for now.
They can enjoy the view of the seagull.
Very nice.
I like it.
I do like it.
I'm a liker of these things.
This is bait, isn't it?
It is.
And then we have this.
It doesn't really fit anywhere, does it?
Nah.
That's kind of trash.
Let's put it in here.
The Ultra Bright Torch.
Let's put the Ultra Bright Torch.
That's hard to say.
Right there.
It's like a little beacon looking over the waves, you know?
Like a little light tower.
Or a light...
Wait, what's the word for that?
Lighthouse.
A lighthouse, of course.
All right.
We go back down now into the underworld.
I don't have a pile on here anymore, unfortunately.
Go there.
Now, I think I have everything I need now.
I have my outfit.
I have this thing now.
Precise...
Wait, who's living here?
Hayley, Ora writes, she's always out in the nature, doing nature things.
Personally, I don't understand all that nature thing.
I'm more into the being inside and gaming thing, if you know what I mean.
That's what I'm about.
All right.
Oh yeah, look at the hens!
Wait, when do they spawn?
It just happens.
Or what?
Like, it just happens?
Let me stand here.
Does it happen here?
Maybe it only happens when you damage an enemy, actually.
Let's see, I'm not going to do anything.
Ah, here we go!
Yo, that did a sick amount of damage!
Oh yeah!
This is going to help me a lot, I think.
It can't not help, if you know what I mean.
Why is it so dark?
Oh, it's because I have the thing on.
I want to keep the thing on, though, in case I spot something out of the ordinary.
Also, there's lanterns tonight?
Is that because I defeated the one-eyed man?
Is that what's happening?
All right, fine.
Let's go down.
Let's drop all the way down.
I wonder if there's any NPC in this game that prefers to live in the underworld.
I would like to make a house down there.
I mean, we already have so many houses.
Maybe I can just, you know, squat in one of them.
Squatter's rights and whatever.
I don't know if that applies to...
Whoa!
What's with the background here?
Is that the biome?
The background behind the map just changed significantly.
Okay, it's a little harder to see down here with this on, I gotta admit.
Let me take it off.
Yeah, it's easier.
See the world...
Forbidden knowledge echoes from the...
That seems like some kind of inside stuff.
For those that know, they know.
Um...
I guess I just explored...
What's...
Oh, there's a bat in the background.
Nevermind.
I guess I just keep exploring.
Let's equip that.
And maybe we find another... thingy.
That's the plan right now.
Just keep exploring, find a doll, maybe find some items.
Who knows.
Where have I gone to?
There.
I wanna explore all the way to the left.
Maybe there's something interesting there anyway.
Stop existing.
You.
Oh, I also gotta be careful.
Why are there so many torches here?
Did I do that?
Did I put all those torches here?
Why is that so torched?
That's weird.
I did loot all this.
Did not loot these though.
Anyway, what I was about to say, I gotta be on the lookout for the demons.
The voodoo demon.
Because they actually carry the doll on them.
So I shouldn't just kill everything immediately.
I gotta be a little careful.
Oh, look, that's a nice painting.
I'll take it.
Shining moon.
That goes in my house.
In my house.
Why am I so slow?
Uh, is it because I don't have the acceleration thing on?
Probably is, isn't it?
Please die.
Thank you.
My minions are doing work.
See, this here...
If you cancel this at the right time, like look, you gain a lot of momentum.
What's that?
I think that's a big deal, I can utilize that.
Like, it's a little hard to do.
Like, look.
It's kind of hard to do, but it's okay.
Kill it!
Gracias.
That one dropped lava.
There's a chest there.
I think I did loot that one.
I kind of remember this chest as well.
Is that crazy?
What about this one?
Of course, I looted everything here.
Okay, so we have now reached the end, or the point where I no longer kept exploring.
Hellfire arrows.
Wait, what is that down there?
That's an interesting flower.
Oh, it was nothing.
Nevermind.
Oh, whoa!
Is this an altar?
I destroyed it.
But I was wondering if it's the same kind of altar as the crimson one.
But just a different variation that allows me to do different things.
It looked like it, didn't it?
It looked a little bit like one of those.
Oh my god, there's a lot of lava here.
This is not the ideal place to fight the boss anyway, actually.
Unless I make a long ass bridge, which I technically could do.
I could just... Honestly, I could make a bridge throughout the entire underworld.
But I don't know, man.
That seems like it would take way too long.
Man, there's nothing over here.
What the fuck?
It's all dead.
What's that?
Oh, it's just a tree.
I keep thinking these are enemies, but they're my friends.
Aha!
Oh no!
I didn't bring the...
Oh.
That's so dumb of me.
Tell me... I don't have it in here, do I?
I'm an idiot.
I completely forgot about that.
That's okay.
Let's just explore to the end here.
Don't shoot that shit at me.
Wait, why am I...
Oh!
Oh, the screen was so... I thought it was in the center of the screen and I thought it was invisible, but I'm over here.
It's because I reached the end.
It's just so weird the way that works.
The screen doesn't follow you anymore.
That's very, very weird.
Alright, well, I've officially made it to the end.
And there's only a single chest here.
Kind of want to dig up towards there, but digging up is a little bit more difficult.
Hold on, I see a little bit of a cave.
I think.
There.
Let's check that out a little bit.
What do we got here?
Take through this.
So, this is kind of slow.
Now, look at this.
Oh, actually, that's the same speed.
Never mind.
Actually, this is quicker.
Ha!
Didn't I discover the opposite at some point?
I don't think I did.
Honestly, I don't remember where I got the doll.
I think it was from the underworld, but I'm honestly not sure.
Yeah, it's definitely faster on these things.
Jesus.
So, when you find gems, that's where you want to use the molten pig eggs.
Oh, oh, shit!
I thought I was obsidianed up.
Just drink that.
Okay.
Go this way.
Let's go.
Wait.
What's happening?
Oh, I reached the end.
Ah, that's why.
Man, when the screen stops following you, it gets so confusing.
Just for a brief second there, all your senses are modeled.
The fiftieth skeleton.
Yeah, okay.
I'm gonna go back up.
Back up for now.
Seth.
Happen...
I just like so many people being close to me.
I'm quite fond of wandering through the forest.
I like it here.
I'm gonna get you a cabin just for you.
Because Seth, you are special, okay?
There's never been anybody like you.
You are one of a kind... person.
Don't you forget it, Seth.
Anyway, where did I find that doll?
Gotta be the underworld.
But it could also actually be something I found over here.
Because...
Didn't I already have a doll before I ever went down here?
I feel like I found a doll way before I ever went to the bottom.
Isn't that how that worked?
I found one from somewhere up here.
Maybe actually over here.
Yeah.
Alright, anyway.
I don't know what to do, honestly, in the game.
I'm a little bit...
lost.
Let's see what we can do.
Defeat the wall of flesh, the master and core of the world who arises after a great burning sacrifice.
Yeah.
Okay.
That is the next step.
Hmm.
And there's also this that I still don't know how to get.
That I want to experiment with.
And I still haven't managed to figure out how to make a pylon here.
I needed people who like the ocean.
That's really it, I think.
That's really it.
In fact, hold on.
Kiboto.
You seem like a jungle man.
Where do you like to be?
Catlin may help your body, but I can make you embody healing.
Oh, help heal...
Oh, nice.
I sort of ruined the joke there.
The close presence of others disrupts my juju and comfort.
Seth, the guide, is a kindred spirit of nature.
My soul is at peace in their presence.
I dislike the practices of Catlin, the nurse.
True healing cannot come from metal and glass.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you're wrong.
None of that hocus pocus shit.
Sort.
Maybe I'll go fish a little bit, actually.
Seems like a good weather for fishing.
And I have crate potions and I also have sonar.
The sonar is somewhere.
There it is.
I have a bunch.
Let's grab some more bait.
Let's go on a crazy fishing trip.
I want to find Ebenkoy.
Scorpions.
Julia butterfly.
Yeah, let's bring all that.
Okay.
Where do you want to try and fish?
How about we try and fish down here?
In the lava.
Huh?
We got to try that.
I also want to try more of the ocean.
But let's go somewhere accessible first.
We never went to the ocean over here, did we?
Ah, we did, but we never went in the water.
That's why it's not explored.
Okay.
I want to fish some more in...
the desert and the jungle.
Let me try both again.
Now that I have all the buffs.
Uh, yeah.
Seems good.
Flip this.
Where is my speed increase thingy?
Ah, there it is.
Let's replace it with that.
Oh man, it's so much better.
Oh my...
This item right here?
The fleeting magi luminescence is actually insane.
Such a good item.
Wow.
The best.
Now I want to use a sword displace.
Crate.
And sonar.
Man, now we're unstoppable.
Eh, hey.
Oops.
This is great.
This is crate.
Nope, don't want the flounder.
I need crates, baby.
Eh, hey.
Kind of cool that I can look at the map while I'm doing this.
Look at this.
I have a whole entourage behind me here.
Hano is also here.
So, Gebato really likes Seth.
And Seth wants to be alone but in the forest.
So, I'm gonna make a little cabin for Gebato and Seth.
Wouldn't crate, thank you very much.
Now, but which forest is the question, right?
Maybe I'll use... maybe this forest over here.
We could also do...
Do we have any... hold on, do we have any more forests, really?
I guess here, yeah, this is... yeah, that would be a good place for it, actually.
Let's do that over there, that'll be the Seth place.
And maybe that's where my home is as well.
Me, Seth and Gebato, we're gonna chill out.
It's gonna be the most wholesome thing ever.
And I'm excited.
You know what, I feel the same way as all those other people that don't want to be crammed into a tiny space with all those.
Random.
I want to be living in the forest with Seth and Gebato.
It's gonna be the best bromance ever.
Come on, give me more crates.
Crates, man.
I wonder if I can get a crimson crate.
Or... Agh!
Eden has arrived!
Hold on, Eden!
What do you sell?
Buy an owain!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Black counterweight, demon horns, dynasty wood, and a katana.
Pars... parsley pells!
That sounds awesome!
Sake.
Oh yeah, I keep forgetting about the food buff.
Why do I... I keep forgetting about this, that's incredible.
Let's head over to the jungle now.
Actually, no, no, no, let's go west.
I think I may get started on the construction of the forest cabin for Seth and Gebato.
Hold on, speaking of Gebato, I can probably see him here now.
Witch doctor!
Oh yeah, he likes... okay, he likes the jungle.
But he likes Seth!
Oh, oh, he doesn't care!
It's just surface!
Right?
Hold on, surface?
There is a difference between surface and just a forest, right?
Isn't there a forest?
Specific forest?
Biome here?
Oh, maybe not.
Maybe surface is forest.
Maybe surface is just the name for the place that is not really a biome.
It's the default, you know?
Fuck.
Hmm.
Yeah, he likes the jungle.
Also, it's funny how...
I was about to say how he doesn't have a name here, he just called Guide, but everyone is actually like that.
The names are actually not in here, it's just the profession.
No.
He's been slain four times!
And what is it about this green cap?
Has he actually dropped this?
Or not?
It says 100%!
I'm still not sure what the stars here mean.
It's like a...
Oh, I just noticed the bar in the bottom!
You can see how many you've collected, that's kind of neat.
I like that.
Alright, so...
I guess I will not put them together.
But I will put Seth all the way over here, away from everybody else.
Because it seems good.
And I also want to try and make a house down here for the old man.
Maybe he will appear, if I make a nice little place for him.
Also...
Let me see here...
What do you actually say?
Seth is not nature, blah blah, I dislike blah...
Yeah, okay.
You don't have a...
You don't say specifically what you want, except jungle.
You want the jungle.
I need crafting materials.
So I need, let's use...
wood.
This is going to be a classic wooden cabin, but with a twist.
I don't actually have any wood.
I'm going to collect it.
Let me grab the glass as well.
Do I have it on me?
I do it, perfect.
Alright, let's go!
Up!
Here we go!
I wonder how long this fishing rod, or this fishing line will go.
This is a...
Oh, okay.
It comes back.
That's fun.
Hey!
So I want to make a house...
there.
Look at this, this is the perfect spot too.
Maybe right by the water, yeah.
Another house right by the water.
That seems awesome.
And I have...
Let me think, how do I want to do this?
I think I want to...
Oh, I have a great idea for a house, for a look.
I want to show you guys the magic here.
Wait, what is...
Oh, this is the beach, right?
Okay.
Go this way.
Let's chop these.
How much do I actually...
Oh yeah, I also have this.
Wait, I got a bunch of stuff.
Is it in here?
Oh, it is.
Where I can run super fast.
Warp 8, nice.
Deposital!
Give me all the bait.
Another crate potion.
No, no, no, no, no.
Sonar.
And...
I think.
Oh, you know what?
It would be cool to try the radio thing here.
Give me the old man.
Oh, I thought I just saw the old man, never mind.
Anything...
Oh yeah, these things.
Get rid of them.
Water candles.
I can't believe I...
I went through most of the dungeon down here.
Before I found out that the...
that the water candles were the ones spawning enemies.
And I only noticed because of the buffs up here.
I should be looking at my buffs some more.
Just in general.
Okay, let's go over here now.
And make the house here.
Do I have dirt on me?
Not really.
Let's grab some from down here.
See how slow this is here?
But this?
Much quicker.
Alright, let's not drain this.
That's a bad idea.
I don't want to drain it.
And though I love draining, there shall be no draining tonight.
Wait, how do I do this again?
There we go.
I gotta take care of these trees, actually.
Dude, I wonder if I go to the snow biome right now, if another one of those will spawn.
What's the time anyway?
Six, twenty...
So, when did he appear?
Was it at a specific time?
He was just doing the night.
Middle of the night.
Twelve o'clock, maybe.
Actually, that could fit.
Oh, I don't have enough dirt.
But you know what?
I do.
I'm just gonna lower it one.
Like that.
Nobody will know.
Nobody will know what happened here.
And the thing...
Okay, here's the plan for the house.
The house is gonna sort of follow the ground a little bit here, okay?
It's gonna be so cool.
So...
Is that all the wood I have?
Bro, I need...
way more.
Are you kidding?
We need to plant some more trees later.
Apple!
Alright.
Get rid of that one.
Let's just take all the trees.
Put them back later.
Okay, now.
This is here.
I'm gonna be doing this.
Oh, you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna put a...
Wait, it's in here.
It's gonna be cool.
There.
Protect me while I build.
Hey!
This is so good.
Yeah!
I don't care about these enemies.
Have fun!
We're gonna do like that and let's make a little bit more space here.
Alright, it's fine.
Build up now.
Actually, no, go one further here.
Something like that.
And it's not gonna be a...
Oh, but wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no.
Change the plan.
This is not what I intended.
I'm gonna change it up a little bit here.
No!
There.
Let me see, is that right?
That's about right.
And then we go like this.
And I have a little bit of...
There we go.
It's gonna be a sick house.
That'd be so good.
Like that.
How do I...
Let's do it like that.
Maybe we should do one higher here.
Dude, I actually really, really love building.
It's like one of the best things about this game.
Similar to Minecraft, it's one of the things that I really enjoyed.
Now we go like this.
Because here's the plan.
Look, we're gonna do something like this.
Oh, wait, that's too much.
Oh, no, wait, this is not what I intended.
Oh, no.
Actually, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Wait a minute.
I'm just freestyling right now, guys.
Don't worry too much.
It's gonna be fine.
And
then...
Wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh...
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know about that.
Hold on.
Fuck it, this looks cool.
Let's do it like that.
And we have a door there.
And then, of course, we need to do this.
And then, oh, we can do this.
Oh, but wait, no, no, no, no, no, wait, this is the issue.
Wait a minute, how do I...
Oh, no, I can't...
Hey, that actually...
That works, sort of.
Wait.
No, I wanted to go one further there.
Like that, and then we go...
Yes, that's it.
Yeah, there we go.
Then we have a door here.
We need a workbench.
There.
Let's make four doors.
There we go.
That seems good.
And then door here.
There we go.
Let's put the background there.
And we have a door over here we can use.
And
then...
I kind of want a little something here.
You know, just a little something.
Nope.
Something like that.
That looks cool.
And now we can do the ultimate trick.
Dude, I'm so glad I figured out this hammer thing.
Actually, game changing.
But wait, it's not aligned.
Fuck!
I'm lazy, so I'm going to do this instead.
And then door.
There we go.
Thank you.
In fact, maybe I'll angle this a little bit here.
There we go.
Because why not?
We're going to have a little bit of a storage area up there.
There we go.
Nice.
And...
That seems good.
Now we need a bunch of wall.
Wall is something that I think I may have.
At home.
But I'm not at home!
Ah!
I could...
nah.
We gotta go with wood.
That's not enough, I don't think.
But fuck it.
Fill it up.
Just put it everywhere.
Actually, it may be enough when we make the rest.
I can make more.
This may be enough.
Okay, up here.
Oh no!
Ah, this is that issue again.
Actually...
Ah man, it looks terrible with this like a little...
It's not completely filled, you know what I mean?
Ah!
That's so annoying!
What?
Is that really how that works?
It's just gonna look like that.
It is what it is.
Now, I want glassware in here, I think.
That's right.
I'm gonna go with glass.
Ah!
And we also need tables and shit.
Let's have a table.
Let's have a table right there.
Ah, let me move that for now.
That workbench can be right there.
Let's have a chair.
There.
We can have a little light.
And this should be a home.
Yeah!
That's your place, buddy.
Please get here quick.
Let me see if you respond.
He does!
Hey!
Also, what's the time?
I kind of forgot about the thing I wanted to do.
Ah, it's too late, I think.
Alright, Seth.
Be advised that certain creatures only come out during rain.
Yeah, I've noticed.
Other creatures, maybe.
Getting this place to myself, I greatly appreciate it.
I'm quite fond of wandering through the forest.
I like it here.
Well, I'm glad, Seth.
I do it for you.
I even put a little turret here for you so you can be protected.
In fact, why don't we put that...
No!
Ah!
Why does it look like this?
Ah, I hate it!
Why is there a little cap in the dirt?
Fuck!
Come on.
No!
Really?
You can't?
What?
No way!
Well, okay, whatever.
I guess you can't.
That looks annoying!
That's annoying me!
Actually, I have a solution to this.
Like, it's working over here.
Oh, it's because of the grass that needs to be grassed there?
Is that what's happening?
Let's just do like this.
Nobody will know.
There we go.
That seems good.
Yeah, you get this place to yourself, and not only that, you're also gonna get a big-ass painting.
There you go!
How do you like them apples?
I know you love them apples.
You're a big fan of apples.
Now, are you gonna...
Oh, but wait, I need another NPC here.
So I can make a pylon.
But wait a minute!
I can't have two forest pylons, right?
Shit!
But you know what I can do?
I can just go here every time, and then run over here.
It's gonna be a little annoying.
But whatever.
Or maybe... Ah, fuck, I don't know.
Maybe it's not a good idea to put Seth here.
I need him every time I craft stuff.
Seth?
You're being evicted.
This is not the home for you?
I have changed my mind.
You should go back to where we came from.
This will be someone else's house.
You're just gonna walk out?
Seth!
No, Seth, don't do it!
I didn't mean... Oh, okay.
We're fine.
I thought he just fucking walked out into the sea and drowned himself.
I'm so sorry, Seth.
I apologize.
I'm gonna put you back here.
Let's... You know what?
This is your room.
There you go.
Are you gonna spawn now?
See, now it works every time.
It's weird.
Oh, I also have this on.
Let's take that off.
Greetings, Oliver.
Is there something I can help you with?
Yes!
Tell me about... stuff.
I guess he already told me everything.
Right, a stylist.
She went off adventuring underground and that was the last I saw of her.
Okay.
So I haven't found the stylist yet.
Maybe I'll try and find the stylist.
I mean, there's probably biomes I haven't discovered yet.
I have not actually ventured underneath this area here.
Even though I've been to a similar area here, maybe something else is going on there.
Right?
Oh, I could also make a house up here, dude.
That could be a cool place.
Speak enough.
Maybe I should explore all this here.
You know what?
I'm gonna do that.
I have potions.
I have the potion required.
Hops!
Where am I?
There.
Okay, let's try.
Okay, that's one of the places.
Then we go down like this.
Let's check out the other side.
Here, the item where you can dash forward is actually useful.
That's the one place where I would say that item is pretty good.
Okay.
You know what?
I bet there's a boss up here.
On one of these islands, that's gotta be a boss.
Right?
Maybe if I plunder all the chests up here, maybe that will be a boss at the end.
Maybe someone's like, how dare you ascend to the heaven and take all my goodies?
Don't you know that's reserved for other people?
People, meaning not me, because I deserve to be in hell for what I've done in this world.
I've murdered countless creatures.
Ah!
There we go!
Hey!
You know, this is already a sweet home, isn't it?
Skymill!
Keen Starfury!
And some other shit.
See the world for what it is.
Wait, Gravity Banner?
Oh,
we already have one of those in here.
This shall become a home here.
This is a home.
This is my home now.
Let's put the skymill there.
What can I do with it?
Probably need sky things.
Harpies!
Pew!
I love this magic missile.
Maybe I can use the feathers in the skymill.
Giant harpy feather.
Ooh, material, huh?
Alright.
We kind of need a light in here.
Let's see here.
Housing is suitable!
So, where am I right now, technically?
Let's look at the map, because it will actually show a background.
We're still in the forest biome, it seems.
Is this the place for Seth?
No, no it's not, no it's not.
Who would, hold on, let's think about this.
Who would like to be up here?
Someone who likes the forest.
Maybe the party girl is up here.
But the golfer, he can golf around up here!
Dude, the golfer?
Let's see here.
Where are you at?
Also, the painter would be a nice spot for the painter, right?
He could have a look over the world and have a nice view to paint.
Bro, where are you?
There, let's see.
Wise middle-aged man who sells all sorts of golfing equipment.
He's got game and knows how to score.
Wow, alright.
Let me look at my notes here.
Did I write something?
He likes the painter, he likes Izzy.
He hates Seymour and he hates...
That's it, pretty much.
Maybe Izzy...
Maybe...
Maybe the painter and the golfer will go together up here, huh?
I kind of... what is the painter's name?
Let's see.
Ludo.
Oh, he likes the jungle.
He drops Jim's cap and a paintball gun.
Alright.
No, let's not put them together.
Maybe... no, Izzy is already at the sea.
Izzy, what is he like?
Oh yeah, the ocean of course.
Yeah, so he stays there.
Let's just put the guy up here, the golfer.
The golfer goes up here.
It's decided.
Where is he?
There it is.
There you go.
Look at all the harpies.
Excuse me.
Man, it is raining feathers now.
Thank you.
What's that?
Oh, it's just a corpse.
Alright, we don't have Gravity Potion on anymore.
Let me quickly go to...
Seth and check out what this feather does.
Hey, Seth!
Tell me about the feather.
A giant harpy feather.
Ah, wait.
Allows flight.
How do I get soul of flight?
There's soul of different things in this game.
And I'm not sure how to get that.
Well, not yet, at least.
See the world for what it is?
Wait, what was that?
I can make these right now?
Sure.
Make that.
Ah...
Get away from me.
Okay.
I guess I'll figure out what the Sky Mill does at some point when Seth tells me.
But for now...
Also, speak enough.
Oh, I can also...
Wait a minute.
Demon wings.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
Well, I'm gonna keep exploring those islands.
Blop.
Let's see.
Do, do, do, do, do.
A little further this way.
Alright.
Let's keep exploring.
Whoa.
I wanna find all the islands.
There's gotta be a boss in one of them.
Well, not necessarily, but...
I think there's a high chance.
So far there's been like a boss in almost every biome, right?
Maybe it's not as obvious at first.
Like the boss in the snow biome was not obvious at all at first.
Until Seth told me about it.
Maybe I have to do something equally crazy there, you know?
Like up here, maybe I have to sacrifice a bird on some kind of sky altar or whatever the fuck.
Oh, I'm in this heavens.
Nice.
Romeo has arrived.
No, he's departed.
Fuck.
But I think I already bought from him.
So everything's fine.
Okay.
Show me the goods.
How long do we have two minutes?
The demons are upside down as well.
With the imps.
I wonder if the fact that you have a different icon depending on the mask you're wearing...
I wonder if that's used in multiplayer a lot so people can put on whatever mask and identify each other on the minimap.
That would make sense to me.
And it looks like we have something here.
There we go.
Just another one.
It's just the same thing every time it seems.
Eye of the sun.
What?
Why can't... Oh, there we go.
Armored celestial magnet?
Wait a minute.
I needed this for something.
Recalls, shine.
There was some kind of crafting thing.
Why I needed that.
Let's just deposit everything into this.
There we go.
Much better.
Wrap these.
Here we go.
Killing again.
Gimme.
Nice.
How did the zombie get up here?
Oh wait, I don't have the thing on anymore.
I feel like there's a minimum separation between these islands, so maybe I should walk a bit longer before I...
But then again, maybe I'll miss one.
Who knows?
Just keep going.
Turn around.
Man, this is such a weird game.
Terraria is honestly a weird game if you think about it.
It's so...
unique.
In its mechanics and what the hell is going on.
But I like it, you know?
It's cool that someone was like, let's just make a cool ass game.
And they did it.
Very unique stuff.
Oh, here we go.
Another one.
What's on this one?
Oops, no entry there.
Another slow star fury and a high pitch.
Is that a big musical instrument?
What's the word for those, like a string instrument?
You know what I mean.
Where are we on the map?
Oh, we're actually soon at the ocean.
That's nice, actually.
I wanted to go there anyway and fish.
Speak enough.
Has there been water on any of these islands?
Because I would love to fish on one of them.
Actually, there has.
Dude, I'm going to go there soon and try fishing.
What the fuck?
Look at that one.
It's almost made for it.
The fuck?
40 seconds, 48 seconds.
I mean, I'm slowly exploring the whole world, I guess.
That's like the progress here.
Both up here and down there.
I'm slowly uncovering this entire game.
So that's nice.
That's like some kind of progression, I guess.
The next big thing for me is to kill the monster of the underworld.
But, man, that thing is fucking hard.
I feel like I really gave it my all and it just wasn't enough.
That is like, honestly, the bosses in this game have been insanely difficult.
Harder than I would have expected.
But then again, I am also playing on...
On something called expert, right?
So I guess I sort of did it to myself.
But there's extra loot to be had.
How can I not?
Can we get one more island?
Uno mas por favor?
Uno mas.
Oh, you know what I'm going to do, though?
So the teleportation potion.
Teleport you somewhere randomly.
I wonder if it can teleport you inside of that temple down there that I don't have access to yet.
Randomly.
By chance.
Who knows?
Maybe it happens, you know?
If it's just a randomized X and Y coordinate in the world.
Could be fun.
Okay, we're almost at the end here.
I have to remember how to craft that potion.
Gotta ask Seth about it.
In fact, I just want to make like...
200 of those and just spam it.
And you know, maybe I find something really cool at some point and like, holy shit!
Like the very first time I tried it, I actually appeared in a new biome.
That I haven't been in before.
That was kind of a neat surprise.
Can we get one last island?
One for the road?
Ah, we're at the ocean now.
There's gotta be one above the ocean.
Right?
There's gotta be.
Also, I just realized, would it be better if I...
Didn't have this on.
Doesn't this slow my fall?
No, it actually doesn't.
Never mind.
But wait a minute, don't I have...
If I remove that one...
No.
Wait, what?
I think it's fall damage, right?
Oh, wait, wait, don't go here yet.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no!
Get out of there.
All right, now I want to go here and try and fish up there.
Oh, actually it's not this one, but okay, that's fine.
Wait, wait a minute.
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's over here.
And here we are.
There we go, let's check it out.
Oh, I don't have any...
Oh, wait, maybe I do actually.
Wait a minute.
Oh, yeah, nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
Beautiful.
Oh, the imps are not enough.
Oh, this is annoying.
Please let me fish in peace, will ya?
Will ya?
Hold on, didn't I also have some nice fishing potions in this chest?
I did.
Oh, this is gonna be painful.
All right, quick!
Fish while they're gone!
What time is it?
4.13am.
Oh, my God.
Oh, please leave me alone.
I'm losing my mind.
Thank you.
Like, I can get maybe one... Wait, was this a chicken nugget?
Did I read that right?
Yeah.
Hey, chicken nugget.
Whoop.
Can you believe that I haven't tried a chicken nugget before maybe one and a half years ago?
I just never did, but I tried it once and I was like, that's all right.
What did I even get?
Where is it?
Chicken nugget.
Oh, a duck!
Sup, duck?
Wait, there's nothing special in this pond.
Come on, man.
Iron... There we go, there we go.
I need more.
Damselfish!
Is it in distress?
Another one.
No, broke!
Gimme.
Kill it!
Nice.
Wooden crate.
I don't want that.
I don't know, I feel like... Is it maybe quicker if I just pull it out?
No, it's not.
I gotta leave it in.
Hey, I'm getting some bunch of wooden crates right now.
Precise tsunami.
Oh, wait, I keep pressing.
That far?
I'm still hoping for a...
Something big inside one of these chests.
Or crates, sorry.
Wait, quack!
That totally sounded like a guy saying quack.
It probably was, wasn't it?
Also, I just got a golden crate, but my line broke.
Like, are you kidding me?
That was very unlucky.
Why are these monsters here?
It's today!
It's so annoying!
I'm standing here, fucking trying to avoid everything.
Bombfish.
I'll take that.
In fact, what if I drain this island?
Huh?
This is the water of the gods.
Actually, it's causing rain.
It's leaking.
The island is leaking.
No, wait, this is a cloud, technically, isn't it?
It was like cloud material when you loot it.
This game is just... even fishing, you have to be avoiding shit on the screen.
Wait, there's nothing special up here, it seems.
Tailfish boots.
Live crystal, wow.
And some masturbate.
Nice.
In fact, I'll use that.
Thank you.
Do we still have... oh, I don't even have a crate thing on anymore.
Where's the potion?
Oh, was it in here?
Sir, give me crate powers.
It seems like this place may be better for golden crates.
There's been two so far, which is kind of a lot in a short amount of time.
Skycrate!
Blessing from the heavens?
Where?
Where is it?
Didn't I just get something called... blessing from... hold on.
What did I just get?
Did he go on my thingy?
Ah!
A painting.
Looks like a...
I don't know, a small hamster in space.
With a... with an antenna.
That's what that looks like.
Get out of here, stupid assholes.
Let me fish in peace.
Bomb fish.
I'll take it.
Ah!
Don't take that.
Okay, the masturbate is actually a very viable technique.
It's totally working.
It's going way faster.
And I say that and then nothing happens forever.
Good timing.
Wait, is it even masturbating right now or not?
What am I using?
Oh, it's using apprentice.
I need to put this first.
It may actually be in here.
You know what?
Depositol.
Quick stack.
Here, open.
I got...
Fuck off and let me fish.
Do I need to mow the fucking snow or what?
Shit, I will mow the heavens.
If you leave me alone.
Jesus!
I really hate this with a passion.
Fuck!
Why do they keep coming?
There's something I'm not understanding.
A base.
Shine potion.
Oops.
Oh, I'm not sonoring anymore.
Frog leg.
Oh.
Sonar.
Fuckin' leave me alone.
Actually annoying.
Give me more sky crates, please.
I want that.
That seems interesting.
Okay, there we go.
Getting some crates.
Yay!
Now we're talking.
At least I can move while I'm fishing, huh?
To dodge this.
Thank you.
Can we grab this?
More.
I refuse to stop fishing.
Let's see how long I can actually fish for.
No, I'm gonna fucking die.
Alright, I'm not gonna fish anymore.
This is just pissing me off right now.
Fuck this shit.
I don't even want to fish up there anymore.
I'm gonna go somewhere else.
Stupid ass birds.
What's up, Haley?
See ya, Haley!
Oh wait, I should have just used my potion.
I'm an idiot.
Eh, it's okay.
Go here, and then we're gonna go to the jungle now.
We need jungle, I'm afraid.
And then I'll try to fish there.
I need all the...
Speaking of fishing, maybe you should talk to Izzy.
Actually, hold on.
While I walk, I'm gonna do this.
Join him in bait, nice.
Oh wait, Izzy is at the ocean.
Fuck.
That's right.
I put him there.
But I can actually, you know what, I can actually get there.
Pretty quickly.
There you go!
Look at that.
Beautiful stuff.
And I can't fish in this, unfortunately.
Already tried it.
That would have been so glorious though, to pull up a magical fish.
A shimmering minnow.
Would be the dream right now.
God, I could go for a shimmering minnow.
You know what I mean?
Up, dip, whoop.
Yay!
There we go.
Whoop, and now we go.
In fact, let's fish at the ocean a bit.
That seems like a chill place, right?
Nobody's gonna disturb us here.
Izzy!
Did you know I have four amazingly awesome fish now?
That's because as far as air monkeys go, you're actually...
So wait, you're keeping track of this!
What's white and tan and fluffy and lives in a frozen underground lake?
And mutant flingspin!
I wasn't telling a joke, you know.
There really is a mutated variety of flings that is more adapted to an aquatic lifestyle.
I want it to adapt to my fishbowl.
So make sure that happens.
Caught in underground tundra.
Mutant flingspin.
Flingspin.
I will get it.
But not now.
Later.
Now, my purpose is to fish from these waters.
And using all the potions I have...
I have sonar, I need crate.
Crate me up.
Here we go.
We're gonna go extra speed.
Which one am I using?
Hold on.
I am using masturbate, perfect.
So let's see how fast this actually goes.
Tuna.
Yeah, I don't think I want tuna either.
Red snapper?
Do I want that?
No.
I do want that.
Depositole.
Swordfish!
Wow, it's a...
It's a sword.
Ha!
Oh yeah, cake!
Fantastic.
Let's not waste the potion.
Hey, seagull, come here.
Ah!
I wanted to piss you with my swordfish.
Fucker.
That would have been so glorious, though, to...
fuck that seagull up.
I don't want trout.
Don't want it.
Don't want tuna either.
Neither.
There's a lot of stuff in the ocean, isn't there?
No!
Why did it break there?
Honestly, in those situations, it's better not to know.
Abraham has arrived.
I will check him out.
What's this?
Oh, the sugar rush.
Man, I could go for some sugar right now.
Yeah, there's not many crates in this here ocean.
This ocean is disappointing when it comes to crates.
There's no crates here.
Nope.
Ah!
Never mind.
Pink jellyfish.
Whoa!
All right.
Oh my god!
See, now the game is giving me crates.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
Oh!
That's got to be a record for me right now.
Finding so many crates in such a short amount of time.
Beautiful.
Farm fish.
Tuna.
Wait, shrimp?
Oh.
Okay, this is a nice place to fish.
There's no enemies.
That is the advantage of this place.
Very nice place to fish.
But it's night now, so will there be enemies?
Now that we have a house here and everything.
The grass has been mowed.
We should be okay, I think.
Ah, here we go.
Yeah, here he comes.
Piece of shit.
Thanks.
What if a star hits an enemy?
I kind of want to see that.
Probably nothing will happen.
Pink jellyfish.
Oh, the sonar is gone.
That's okay.
More of a surprise, isn't it?
And in the end, it may actually take the same amount of time.
There we go.
See, that could have been an amazing crate, but I will never know.
And that's maybe a good thing, because the lion broke.
Another swordfish.
Hold on, is the swordfish a material?
It's not.
Okay.
I have many crates to open.
You know what, let's open them now.
In fact, I actually got to end it here, because it's been a while.
I got to eat.
No, don't throw the crates!
I can actually put the...
Oh, I can even...
Hey!
Cool.
Hunter potion.
More masturbate.
Sixteen gold?
Dude.
Nineteen gold?
In a crate?
This is a legit way to get money!
Like, what?
How is that not incredible?
Uh...
Did I have more?
No.
Uh, will you stop knocking on the...
I'm gonna swordfish you.
Get away!
That's what you get.
That'd be a lesson.
To you and all future zombies trying to get here.
Uh, what is that thing right there?
What is that?
Oh!
It's... it's the vault.
I'm an idiot.
Oh my god.
Ah!
Wow.
Well...
Dude, I really wanna kill...
the fucker down here.
But that's gonna happen next time.
For now, I'm actually gonna go straight to the store and get some food.
Actually, no, that's not true!
I have food at home!
Fuck yeah.
So I'm gonna eat that now.
Uh, people!
Let me quickly check...
if everything is still working fine.
Isanti!
The one-eyed man is back, baby!
That's right!
Nice.
It's become sort of a meme on this channel by now.
It's awesome.
Thank you for the five euros, Isanti.
Once again, I appreciate it.
I hope you all enjoyed the stream.
I had a lot of fun once again exploring this world...
that I think by now I'm sort of getting to the end of.
I have a feeling that the underworld man may be the end of things.
Because think about it, realistically.
I've explored most of the map.
I mean, when I say most of, I mean like biomes and stuff, right?
And the whole underworld is sort of explored.
The whole overworld is sort of explored.
There's only the in-between.
So, I'm looking forward to killing the wall of flesh.
So!
I'm gonna end it here, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
You guys are amazing.
I will see you in the next stream...
later this week.
So, a big thanks to all of you for being here.
Adios!
Bye-bye!